So in this shock, you are able to log in if you go to account, log in.
You will need an email address and a password.
Now often it's the case that user names are displayed in public.
So that means that you can.
And also email addresses can often be found on the website themselves and to log in, all we need is
an email address and a password.
Right?
So one thing you can do is to click around on the websites and try to find email addresses.
So you'll see you have a lot of options here in the sites, and by clicking around, you will be able
to find email addresses.
On the websites and so those email addresses can be used to log in.
So that's the first task.
So let's go in so that if we click on any of the products, you'll note that there's a review section
and you'll see there are email addresses so we can start collecting them
and you'll see if we click through them.
We the second product already shows the administrator accounts email right.
So that will be the email we need to log in into the website so you can collect them all.
If you go through the products, you get all the email addresses.
So of course, the main interesting one is the admin accounts, but you'll see there are several orders.
You'll see many more email addresses.
So often times things like logging information usernames can be found in public, like in reviews and
gets this case of the products, and your guests can get all those kind of email addresses or usernames
which are required to log in.
So then we already have half of the information to log in.